riskdisk.com 2012-10-05

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
1. The Privacy Policy lays out the relevant data processing techniques
employed in delivering the Riskdisk.com service to you.
2. You will be requested to supply information to us in using the web site
and we will collect details of this and from any emails you may send us.
These will be the only personal details we collect and store from you. In
order to provide the web service, we, like all web service providers you
use, will be aware of your IP address.
3. We employ a range of measures including encryption and coding to
take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information and that
we receive and store your details confidentially and securely.
4. The information you supply to us will be used for providing the service
subscribed for, or a demonstration of it to you, responding to your
enquiries, informing you of additions or amendments to the service, and
invoicing you.
5. We will only disclose your personal information if required by law to
the Police, the Government, the Data Protection Commissioner, the Office
of Fair Trading and if required under a contract with an information
supplier or bank.
6. We may use ‘Cookies’ in providing service to you. A cookie is a small
amount of data which is sent to your browser. Your browser may store it
on your PC. You can control whether or not you wish your browser to do
so. If you do not accept cookies on your PC, there may be restrictions in
the service you receive.
7. Transmitting information over the internet uses telecommunications
and computer processing outside of our control. By using our service
through your browser you acknowledge that we are entitled to use the
internet to deliver service to you.
